On a Ws console, go to the search bar
and type Cloud Shell.
Cloud Shell and take click on the cloud shell.
I can Here now click on close Next code to actions here.
Click on upload file. Now click on this particular script.
Now this script I would've given you already right
below or about this video.
Download that and it'll upload that
sh file the shell script.
It's uploading right now. It's all done. Or type Ls.
Next type s sh space.
Copy this one. Right click.
Copy right here, paste and enter.
Next, click on actions and go to delete and type, delete.
Next, go to search bar type S3
and click on the S3 link here.
And then scroll down. You'll see the bucket right here.
Click on the bucket name. Next. Click on the create folder.
Type the folder name as raw and scroll down.
Click on create folder. Click on refresh button.
You should see the raw folder here.
Now go inside the folder Raw. Again, create the folder.
Name it as F-E-F-H-E. Why?
Because we're actually uploading the H high volume
for higher vehicle data inside the folder.
So scroll down and create the folder. Again, refresh.
Click on the folder. Just click on Upload Next,
click on add files.
Go to the folder where you have the power
download and click on open.
It'll show up like this. Scroll down, click on upload.
This will take a few minutes after it's uploaded,
you should see like this shows a hundred percent here,
and you click on this link here.
You should see the file right here.